



Gökay Özsoy

Date of birth: 02/03/1999 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Phone number:**

(+49) 15754860837 (Mobile) | Email address: gokayozsoy0@gmail.com | Website:

https://gkyzsy.github.io/

Address: Borsteler Chaussee 72, 22453, Hamburg, Germany (Home)

ABOUT ME

Computer Engineer / Junior Software - Web Developer

I am a computer engineer with experience in various areas. I love developing creative software and maintaining code & databases. My main programming language is JavaScript at the moment. I have recently developed a 2d action-packed web game using vanilla JavaScript, HTML5 Canvas, CSS, and Sprite animations. Feel free to check it on my portfolio link!

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

17/09/2017 - 03/07/2023 Ankara, Türkiye

COMPUTER ENGINEERING TED University

Website https://www.tedu.edu.tr/en | Field of study Information and Communication Technologies |

Level in EQF EQF level 6 | National classification 6 | Type of credits ECTS | Number of credits 246

WORK EXPERIENCE

25/08/2024 - 21/09/2024 Berlin, Germany

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN KREATIVSTORM

- Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)
- WRSPM Model
- Methodologies (Waterfall, Agile, Kanban, etc.)
- Microservices
- API

Email contact@kreativstorm.de | Website https://www.kreativstorm.de/

08/08/2022 - 11/08/2023 Ankara, Türkiye

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ZKR NURSE CALL SYSTEMS

- Developed web forms and maintained and customized database for customers to observe user data. Maintained both front-end and back-end sides of projects by taking account of customer feedback.
- Arranged regular meetings with customers around the world. Planned the scope of Integration projects.
- Provided IT support through video calls and remote connection software (AnyDesk, TeamViewer).
- Developed a system management application on Linux to improve the production line's performance and to make basic daily operations easier.

Business or Sector Information and communication

Address Umit Mahallesi, Okullar Sokak, No.16, 6810, Ankara, Türkiye | Email info@zkr.com.tr |

Website https://www.zkr.com.tr/

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN ZKR NURSE CALL SYSTEMS

- Learned frequently used technologies, tools, and programming languages in the company such as Qt Creator, PHP, JavaScript, C++, MySQL, etc.
- Handled the configurations of the company's products.

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web

JavaScript | JSON | CSS | PHP | Linux | SQL | Angular | NestJS | MySQL | HTML5 canvas | HTML

Back-End / Embedded / Desktop

Qt | C++ | Java

Network

TCP-IP | VoIP Systems

Version Control / Methodologies

Github | Git | DevOPS (basic level)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): TURKISH

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

CERTIFICATES

29/01/2024 - CURRENT

Information Technology Fundamentals by IBM

Link https://www.credly.com/go/Ymql10QM

26/01/2024 - CURRENT

Web Development Fundamentals by IBM

Link https://www.credly.com/go/ky06KxyH